[Forging Justice]
[Episode 14]
These are three human lives,
Mei.
How come there are three?
If he's convicted,
Qian Xingliang
will definitely get the death penalty.
Then who exactly is the deceased?
We don't even know whether Yu Sanhua
is dead or not.
Xia.
This case
is a decent one I finally got
after enduring things here
for three years.
I value it
very highly.
I know.
That's why I'm eagerer to help you.
How can you help me?
By asking me to return the files?
The difference between us now
is too great.
We also won't be able to
try it well in court,
and we may even make a fool of ourselves.
How about this?
Go find the chief judge,
the court president or other superiors.
Let them decide
which of us will stay or leave.
As long as the leaders say it,
I'll obey unconditionally.
Mei.
It doesn't have to be either of us leaving
or staying here, does it?
Yes, it does.
That is a way to show full respect
for both of us.
Are you going or not?
If you're not going, I will.
Fine.
I'll go.
Yu.
I think
this case
should be handled according to the files
sent by the procuratorate.
Let's not complicate the matters.
Court Pres.
I understand what you mean.
I quite appreciate your sense
of justice.
But...
Court Pres.,
let's put aside the sense of justice
and just talk about
the realistic problems.
Okay.
If we leave room for flexibility
in this case,
not only will it fail to
solve the public-opinion issue,
but it will also bring us hidden dangers.
As for Song Xiaoguang's
disguise of mental illness,
anyone with a discerning eye
can sense it instantly.
If we back down now,
people outside will all gossip about
how powerful men
can gain everything they want.
But Court Pres.,
if we handle it strictly,
not only can we preserve
the reputation of our Intermediate Court,
but we can also
set a standard for
similar related cases.
If things go well,
it's naturally due to your
excellent leadership
as the court president.
If it doesn't go well...
Don't worry.
I will ensure that
everything is signed and documented.
If the superiors hold us accountable,
I will be the first to step forward.
Court Pres.
In short,
if we succeed,
we'll be heroes upholding justice.
If we release
that maniac now,
you will inevitably have to
clean up their mess later.
What do you mean by cleaning up a mess?
Be more civilized.
What you said
does make some sense.
However,
if we openly challenge
this matter now,
wouldn't it be inappropriate?
It's certainly good to be able to
analyze the situation
and have political sensitivity.
But if there are
no good solutions,
then...
Court Pres.
There is actually a solution.
Otherwise, I wouldn't have come to you.
Yu.
How many years have you
been working here?
Over three years.
Then tell me
what the solution is.
Okay.
These are really good today.
-The filling is good.
-Yummy.
Taste it.
Lihui.
What are your plans next?
Won't you consider getting a Ph.D.?
I only want to apply
to be your doctoral student.
Is that okay, sir?
That's great.
You are welcome to apply.
Hey, cheers.
Cheers.
It's a deal.
But, Lihui,
I have a small suggestion.
If you study for a Ph.D.,
you shouldn't work at the same time.
I'm afraid I still have to.
What's more, it'll take a few years
before I come back to get a doctorate.
That's fine, too.
Why is that?
Do you have a boyfriend?
No.
I'm being transferred to another place.
Where will you go?
In a few days,
I'll go to the Xijiang Procuratorate
to report for duty.
That's good, too.
Getting experience
in a provincial procuratorate
is not a bad idea.
It's an even lower-level institution.
I'll go to Bieshan Prison
to be a resident prosecutor.
Where?
Prison?
Whose idea is this?
Who decided this?
Isn't this so wicked?
As a girl,
why are you going to work in a prison?
Zhou.
Aren't they all your students?
For example, that person
and so-and-so.
Go ask them.
What mistake did Lihui make?
Why are they exiling Lihui like this?
I'm not being exiled.
Ma'am, I requested it myself.
Have you suffered any injustice?
It has nothing to do with anyone.
I decided it myself.
Then tell us your reasons.
My reasons
are not that complicated.
I just feel that
once I graduated,
I went to work
at the Supreme People's Procuratorate,
so I've had
no practical experience at all.
I didn't think much of it
in the first few years.
But in the past two years,
I've found it more and more
necessary to make up for
my missed lessons.
But there's no need to go so far.
Ma'am,
since I'm going to
a grassroots institution,
I'd better go to the lowest-level one.
Silly child.
You're thinking of it too simply.
If you go so far,
can you still come back?
I haven't thought about that.
Lihui,
you can't act wilfully like this.
M-Ma'am, please don't be like this.
Alright. Let's eat.
Good, good, good!
Good!
Run! Run!
Come on!
Let your feet move more agilely.
What?
Are you here specifically to thank me?
Not specifically.
I just want to thank you
for helping me last time.
There are also many questions
I haven't asked.
I think I can ask you again this time
when I'm here.
But they're unrelated to that case.
Do I have to answer?
I don't care. I'm asking.
Here's the first question.
Has your leg been like this
since kindergarten?
Last time, when a person asked me that,
I took a glass of water
and pour it on his face.
You know I mean no harm.
Polio.
It's been like this since I was three.
Here's the second question.
Do you sit here every day
watching them play basketball?
I'm their coach.
You're their coach?
Even though I can't even shoot a ball,
I understand tactics.
What's more, I would encourage them.
They all listen to me.
Our team has no rival
in the nearby compounds.
You can play basketball too, right?
You saw it last time, didn't you?
I was the captain
of our school team,
the President of the Student Union
and a cadre.
I'm the chosen one.
That's impressive, huh?
Then why were you assigned
to this small place of ours?
Did you make a huge mistake?
There was something fishy
about the assigning process?
I may not know about other things,
but I have
a good political background.
Let's go.
Let's play basketball.
Let's play basketball!
Be careful.
What?
Give it to me.
Try it.
Just hold it like this.
When you shoot, use this hand
to support it.
Then do it like this. Bend your arm.
When you use your strength in the end,
press it with your middle three fingers.
Give it a try.
Then I'll do this now.
Come on! Come on! Come on!
It's fine.
It's actually very good
for your first time.
No rush. Take your time.
Come on!
I'm doing it!
Come on! Come on! Come on!
I almost made the shot.
Try again.
Come on!
Lihui.
While making major life decisions,
you might be impulsive.
But you mustn't act out of spite.
Sir.
I'm not acting out of spite.
I'm just not very satisfied with myself.
The more I try to maintain
my dignity on the surface,
the more it makes me look
weak and hypocritical.
Sir,
don't worry.
I've made this decision
not because I want to put on
a tragic play for myself.
I genuinely
want to change myself.
Alright then.
I'll support you.
I have always felt that
judges and prosecutors
should be the professions
with the highest thresholds in the world.
Because they have to judge and decide
other people's lives.
If a person doesn't have
an independent personality
and always feels inferior,
he indeed can't
become a qualified judge
or prosecutor.
The meaning and value
of our work
is to protect
the lives and dignity
of those ordinary individuals
and to promote goodness
for the entire society.
Think about it.
Is there anything
more meaningful than this?
I will definitely become
the kind of person you mentioned, sir.
Definitely.
[Beijing Station]
Dear passengers,
welcome to Beijing Railway Station.
Our station is dedicated to providing
good travel services for all passengers.
Please comply with the station's rules
and regulations
while waiting for your trains.
I need to make a phone call.
One yuan if they call back,
30 cents if they don't.
Okay.
Hello, page 0487. My surname is Yu.
It's urgent. Please call back immediately.
Sir.
Is there any place nearby
that's suitable
for treating someone to a meal?
Yes.
See the one up there?
It provides Cantonese food
and fresh seafood.
I'll leave the money here.
It's very classy. I'm telling you.
Just one lobster there
costs as much as what I earn
by selling newspapers for three months.
Are there any places
that are more affordable?
Young man,
if you're trying to get things done,
Cantonese food is the classiest.
Okay. I'll be waiting for a call.
Tell me when they call back.
I'm right around here.
Okay.
As for this steamed fish,
could you get a smaller one for me?
I'm sorry, sir.
The smallest fish we have here
is over 1.5 kilograms.
But the two of us
can't eat up a 1.5-kilograms fish.
That's enough. Don't order it.
I don't like fish.
What about the wine?
What wine should we drink?
This one.
Stop looking at this.
I can't drink.
I have to work this afternoon.
Okay.
Alright. That's all for now.
Okay. Thank you.
Yu Gaoyuan.
This meal
will cost you several hundred yuan.
What's wrong with you?
Aren't you going to live your life?
When treating someone to a meal,
shouldn't I do it properly?
I've even brought my bankbook.
Have some tea.
Chief Judge.
She's not even as good as Sun.
Whatever she says is right,
and whatever I say is wrong.
On what grounds could she do this?
Just because she graduated
from a prestigious university?
But I graduated from Dongdu University
of Political Science and Law, too.
Chief Judge,
didn't you also graduate from that school?
Yes, yes, yes.
Anyway, regarding this case,
I definitely won't return the files.
Xia.
Why are you standing here?
Nothing, nothing.
There's a misunderstanding between us.
Let's clear it up today.
What happened between Lihui and me
wasn't really like...
Alright. Stop talking about it.
It has nothing to do with me indeed.
But as a lawyer,
I more or less
have a sense of justice.
What's more, it's all in the past.
When I said
I'd cut ties with you that day,
it was just liquor talking.
Okay.
Zhang Lihui is not
at the Supreme People's Procuratorate.
She went to Xijiang. Do you know that?
What happened?
I really didn't know about this.
Is it because of what happened before?
Do you think you're so important?
Why does everyone
have to be connected to you?
Can't she have her own
aspirations?
Yes, she can.
Why are you...
Are you here this time
specifically to see me
and treat me to a meal?
I'm here specifically to see you.
I need your help
with a case.
Yu Gaoyuan, what's wrong with you?
Do you want to quit wearing this uniform?
I think you need to continue to
participate in this case.
But right now,
my conflict with Mei has escalated.
She couldn't wait anymore
and just went to
see the chief judge herself.
She probably wants to
transfer me away from here.
Then don't escalate the conflict.
Just compromise with her
and say some nice things to her.
Why should I do that?
Are you insisting because you believe
she's wrong,
or you think it's a life-and-death matter,
so you can't be careless?
To be honest,
both are the reasons.
If you want to prove she's wrong,
it doesn't matter if you quit.
Because this matter
is actually meaningless.
What's more, whether she's right or not
is not for you to decide.
Only time will tell.
Maybe in the end,
she's not wrong at all,
and you just overthought it.
I think you've misunderstood me.
It's precisely because
I don't know the answer
that I don't want to
treat human lives carelessly.
If you don't want to
treat human lives carelessly,
you have do everything you can
to continue to participate in this case.
Currently, criminal trials in China
are still investigation-centered.
If there are unresolved issues
during the investigation stage,
it is basically impossible
for you to rely on
the presiding judge to turn the tide
in court.
Moreover, that wouldn't be
fair to the litigants.
It's too dangerous.
As for this case,
Qian Xingliang
needs to find a good lawyer.
He does have an appointed lawyer now.
In this kind of case,
do you think an appointed lawyer
can help?
I don't know.
If you want to continue to
participate in the case,
listen to me.
Go back and apologize to her,
even if you have to
say some hypocritical words.
Well,
everyone knows the tricks
of playing along.
I'm just usually unwilling to fake it.
You're unwilling to fake it?
You...
don't have to fake it in front of me.
Why don't you practice first?
Just practice with me.
Say some...
Say some hypocritical words
that you normally wouldn't say.
Let's do it.
W-What should I say?
Just pretend this is...
a date for us today.
And you're going to
confess your love to me.
Go ahead.
You can't even say a word?
So childish.
Got it.
To catch the prime culprit,
Song Xiaoguang,
you need to find a lawyer
who dares to speak out
to defend those minions,
voice grievances for them
and complain about unfair verdicts.
Only then can you guys legitimately
propose a re-appraisal, right?
Good for you.
This is what you're like indeed.
What a smart calculation.
By setting a trap for Song Xiaoguang
and using us as a tool,
you guys will offend no one
and take all the benefits
with no risks at all.
If Song Xiaoguang is convicted,
you'll be the righteous judge
upholding justice for the people.
What if we lose the lawsuit?
Even if you lose the lawsuit,
won't you still get the attorney's fees?
Give me a break.
You think Mr. Yuan is working for charity?
To handle a case like this,
we won't even earn enough
to pay for this meal.
Then what?
Do you agree to let Mr. Yuan handle it?
No.
Wait a moment.
You...
How much is the attorney's fee
you just mentioned?
I've asked around.
The family member
of one of the victims
is a businessman.
They are quite well-off
and can offer a lot of money.
His daughter was ruined by Song Xiaoguang
and eventually committed suicide
by jumping into the river.
I...
We're not doing this for money.
Sometimes justice is quite expensive.
Right?
We lawyers need to make a living too,
don't we?
Let me tell you.
This case has already
gone to trial.
Those accomplices
have their own defense lawyers.
If they want to
change their defense lawyers,
it'll be a bit difficult.
But it's not impossible.
If you guys want to
take this case,
you'll have to start from
the civil compensation for the victims
and use it as an entry point.
You've thought this all out.
This meal of yours
isn't a waste at all.
I was on the train for two days.
It took me more than 10 hours.
I had to stand for over 10 hours.
I'm going back tonight.
If I can't get anything out of this chat,
wouldn't this trip be in vain?
Why are you in such a hurry?
Aren't you going to visit Mr. Cheng
and Mr. Zhou?
They usually pay a lot of attention
to you.
What is it about me
they'd pay attention to?
It would be fine
as long as they don't laugh at me.
They would pay attention to me?
What? Shall I go over there
and say, "Thank you both
for assigning me to Binjiang"?
What you're thinking is too extreme.
Even if they had not
assigned you to Binjiang
and had assigned you
to the Supreme People's Court
or the Supreme People's Procuratorate,
what would you do then?
W-Would you be able to take on
such a big case?
My parents will go to Binjiang
in a couple of days,
so I need to go back there in advance.
Lu,
put aside
your personal prejudice against me.
In this case,
no matter how I plot,
eventually, my purpose
is still to arrest Song Xiaoguang
and put him in the dock.
As for other things,
I don't care what you say about me.
There aren't many people I can trust.
You are one of those I trust,
and Mr. Yuan is another.
Why do you trust me?
I stink of money.
I don't care
whether you stink of money or not.
Li Xiang's case
has always been in my mind.
So you're done eating?
I'm full.
Waiter, the bill, please.
Coming.
How much?
136 yuan in total.
136 yuan.
Here.
Okay.
I've noticed that your wallet
is made of leather.
♪ I'll hold your hand tightly, my friend ♪
♪ The night sky is far away ♪
♪ Looking at the starlight,
we are closely connected ♪
♪ Even if there would be thorns
all over the roads ahead ♪
♪ Untie the loneliness in my heart ♪
♪ Who can understand me? ♪
♪ We're like hands ♪
♪ Being happy and sad together ♪
♪ And we always share the burden ♪
Alright.
I'll be waiting for your messages.
♪ You would do anything for me ♪
♪ I would do anything for you ♪
♪ When we face difficulties
in despair together ♪
♪ I'll hold your hand tightly, my friend ♪
Sir.
The gentleman in the suit
already paid the bill just now.
I'm returning this to you.
Please pack the food for me.
Okay.
I'm leaving now.
Come on.
Be quick.
Buns, rice and steamed bread.
We have everything.
Freshly steamed buns.
Sun.
Prosecutor Chen.
Here.
Have a pancake.
How come his restaurant is reopened?
His brother-in-law
took over the restaurant.
Taste it.
I'm really not eating it.
Then you can also reopen your restaurant.
Why are you setting up a stall here?
I don't have the energy for that.
My family is in such a state.
And I don't have the capital, either.
Taste it.
Today, I'm here
because of this.
People in our workplace
chipped in some money.
All the details are inside here.
Take this for now
to treat your wife's illness.
Freshly steamed buns. They smell great.
No, no.
I can't take this money.
I only have one request for you.
Hurry up and bring them to trial.
Give them a severe sentence soon,
and I'll be satisfied.
I understand.
But treating your wife's illness
is more important.
Don't worry about anything else for now.
-Okay?
-No, no, no.
Dad!
What's wrong?
My mom is missing.
Where is your mom?
You didn't use the rope.
What do I need you for?
Why are you hitting the child?
Tell me.
Tell me!
I noticed that she was suffering too much.
Being tied up with a rope,
she was in great pain.
Didn't I know she was in pain?
Alright, alright!
I...
-Now just think about...
-I...
Now just think about
where your wife might be.
Okay?
How would I know where she is?
I... I...
She's a living person.
Bridge piers.
The bridge piers.
Whenever I argue with her,
she would run to the river.
Let's go.
Shuzhen!
Mom!
Sun Lai!
Are these your mom's shoes?
My mom does have
a pair of shoes in this color.
Did she wear them today?
I don't remember.
You're so useless!
What do I need you for?
Is that her?
I think so.
Prosecutor Chen!
I can't swim.
Go... Go call for help!
She's right there!
Okay. Alright.
Hurry up!
Don't let her drift away!
Shuzhen!
Are you still feeling unwell?
Take good care of your mom.
Okay.
I'm aware of the situation now.
Prosecutor Chen.
Thank you.
Thank you for saving our entire family.
I also don't know why our family
got caught up in this.
It's endless.
Today,
I almost made you sacrifice your life.
It's fine, Mom. It's fine.
It's fine.
It's fine. It's fine.
Thank you.
Mei,
you got a meal from the cafeteria again?
Why not go home and make some nice food?
I'm alone, so I don't want to cook.
Even if I cook, I would still eat alone.
What a waste of time and energy.
My husband is dead.
My hometown is not in Binjiang, either.
Nor do I have many friends.
My life
is probably just going to be like this.
Have some water.
Mei.
I went back and thought about it.
I'll listen to you.
Let's not return the files for now.
We'll proceed with the trial as normal.
Xia.
Are you serious?
That's great.
Well...
W-What happened?
Did someone persuade you?
Was it the chief judge?
But Mei,
can we discuss it?
By then,
let's not make a ruling immediately.
After the trial, let's think carefully,
render a decision cautiously
and try to make it foolproof. Okay?
Okay.
Absolutely.
If you had said this earlier,
we wouldn't have had any conflicts.
Xia.
Thank you, Xia.
Thank you.
When you come back from Beijing,
go to Daoxiangcun
and buy some sponge cakes
and walnut cookies for my dad.
He loves those pastries.
I'm afraid I won't have enough time.
Okay.
I promise I'll finish the task.
That's more like it.
Extra points for you, silly man.
Got it.
Have you been to Beijing before?
I used to go there when I was a kid.
When my dad went on business trips,
he often took me with him.
Did you like it?
It was okay.
Come back soon.
Give me a kiss.
The kids are watching.
Can't they see us?
No, they can't.
Have some peanuts.
Spit it out.
I'm swamped by work here.
It's a case, too.
Could you handle it for me?
No.
You just refused it without even asking?
I have a lot of work to do.
There are loads of non-litigation business
for me to handle.
As the legal counsel for the Snail Group,
I get paid monthly in US dollars.
Don't I have to make money
to support your righteous cause?
Lu,
l-lawyers' lawsuits can't
just be handled for money.
Well, you... you...
Lawyers can't
just handle lawsuits for money.
Mr. Yuan, we've already divided it up.
You're in charge of handling free cases
while I have to
take on profitable cases, right?
This case is profitable, too.
This case is also profitable.
How much is this?
200 yuan.
200 yuan is fine.
A village secretary, who is also a bully,
has been using violence
to forcibly occupy villagers' land
for a long time.
I won't take the case.
You...
What's wrong with 200 yuan?
That's worth two months' salaries.
You won't take the case, huh?
Who paged me?
Lu, it's me.
No wonder I've been
sneezing so much lately.
Stop joking.
I have a case here.
Can you take it?
So you're doing the same thing
as Yu Gaoyuan?
Did he contact you too?
Song Xiaoguang?
No.
Mine isn't about Song Xiaoguang.
It's about Qian Xingliang.
Mr. Yuan.
Just get to the point.
I have a case.
I'm very busy.
I have many cases here.
And I don't understand your cases.
You are good at this kind of case.
What's more, it's profitable.
This amount.
How much?
3,000 yuan?
Can't you be more
ambitious?
How am I not ambitious?
I can get 3,500 yuan here.
I can earn 3,500 yuan from my four cases.
I-It's just 3,000 yuan,
and you want me to handle it?
How could you say something like that?
You can earn 3,500 yuan
from these four cases.
That's not even a fraction of mine.
What do you mean
by not even a fraction of yours?
But I have four cases.
I can earn only 3,500 yuan
from these four cases.
What's more, each one is harder
to deal with than the last.
What?
Um, you have four...
You have four cases.
How did you do the math?
What kind of math am I supposed to do?
Regarding these four cases,
each one is harder
to deal with than the last.
Over 30 migrant workers,
over 200 villagers
and a private school teacher
are all waiting for me
to seek justice for them.
I'll get only 3,500 yuan.
Is it worth it?
But you even want me
to handle this 3,000-yuan case?
Do you think I'm still...
I'm still charging 200 yuan?
Then let me
put it another way.
A man who has been running amok for years,
harming dozens of women
and girls,
has a powerful background
with high-ranking officials in his family.
With a psychiatric evaluation report,
he can be exempt from prosecution
and escape legal punishment.
Millions of people in the city
are expecting you, Mr. Yuan,
to step up and bring this
wicked guy to justice.
There is a western proverb.
Laws are like cobwebs,
which may catch small flies,
but let wasps and hornets break through.
Mr. Yuan, do you think
we can allow
such things
to happen
in our socialist China too?
Can we allow it?
Shouldn't we arrest this kind of person?
Go on.
Do you think this case is urgent or not?
Isn't it exciting?
Hearing what I've said, are you tempted
to take it?
G-Go on.
What else can I say?
A bully
harmed dozens of women.
Relying on his family's background,
he got himself
a psychiatric evaluation report.
Then no one can do anything about him.
Alright.
H-How much is this case of yours?
You just said mine
is not even a fraction of yours.
H-How much is it exactly?
30,000 yuan.
30,000 yuan?
Okay.
I, Yuan Yifang, am going to
prove myself, too.
I can also earn 30,000 yuan
from a lawsuit.
It's not about the money.
Justice is priceless.
D-Don't talk about that with me.
Go get the case files for me.
So how many cases do I
have to handle now?
[1988, Linshan]
[Shaling, Xinghu, Moping]
Are you from Beijing?
You're going to Bieshan, aren't you?
Prosecutor.
Is your name Zhang Lihui?
That's right. Let's go.
Let's go.
What are you doing? Who are you?
What's your name?
Do you have your work ID?
I'm here to pick you up.
Your work ID.
I know you're from Beijing,
and you're going to Bieshan.
You're a prosecutor.
What's wrong?
So you don't trust me?
Do I look like a bad guy?
Everyone thinks this is novel
when first arriving here.
But after two months,
they would all clamor to go back.
After a year,
they would all cry and shout,
"I'll never come back here again
for the rest of my life!"
Who are you talking about?
I'm talking about all the people
I've ever picked up.
Did you offend a superior?
No.
Did you get dumped?
No!
Alright.
Then you're here for the subsidy.
The subsidy here in Bieshan
is indeed higher
than that in other places.
So you have a heavy family burden?
I'm not married,
and I don't have a family.
Then as a young woman,
why are you going to Bieshan?
For work.
For work?
There's no work there.
Everyone there is serving a sentence.
Those who are inside the walls
are serving life sentences,
while those who are outside the walls
are serving fixed-term sentences.
The minimum sentence is three years.
If a person can endure it
for even two years,
then he's really tough.
Normally,
rotations are required every year.
That prison
actually doesn't even need guards.
It's not necessary.
Why?
Two years ago,
an prisoner climbed the wall and escaped.
They searched for five days and found him.
His corpse
was less than 500 meters
away from the prison.
Why?
Was his leg injured?
He just got lost.
It was like being trapped in a maze.
In the end, he died of thirst.
The soles of his shoes
were completely worn out.
Actually,
he was just near the prison,
walking in circles in the Gobi Desert.
Five days,
500 meters.
It's fine, girl.
Once you get there,
just stay put and don't wander off.
After you endure it for three years,
you'll be able to adapt wherever you go.
No matter who you meet again,
it'll just be like meeting your family.
Left, face!
Double time, march!
Here we are.
[The Procuratorate Office‌ in Bieshan Prison,
Xijiang Province Bieshan Prison]
Thanks for your hard work.
Thanks for coming all this way.
Mr. Guo.
I've brought her here for you.
You can check.
Not a single piece is missing.
He didn't scare you on the way, did he?
He always tells others
that an escaped prisoner
ran five kilometers in three days.
Wasn't it 500 meters in five days?
You brat!
You haven't changed, have you?
This is Mr. Guo.
You guys got three years' imprisonment.
He got life imprisonment.
Shoo!
My name's Guo Dajie.
I'm a resident prosecutor here.
I've been working here for over 20 years.
These brats always make fun of me,
saying that I got life imprisonment.
Zhang, right?
Zhang... Zhang Lihui.
Yes.
Welcome.
Hello, Mentor.
Hello. Don't call me that.
Don't call me Mentor.
Just call me Comrade.
Thank you.
Here are the documents and medicine.
Okay, okay, okay.
Please don't mind it.
Just stay here tonight.
I don't want to spend a night
in a prison.
I'm going back to the town.
Okay.
Just go.
Alright.
Miss,
take care.
Drive safely.
Okay.
Alright.
Give it to me.
I can carry it myself.
Just give it to me.
I'll hold it for you.
-Give it to me.
-Thanks, Mentor.
Let's go.
Don't call me Mentor.
Come on in. Come on.